

MARCIN WRZOŚ

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PORTFOLIO

PROFILE

I have experience in working on non-commercial projects with senior developers. I am a person who is characterized by a 'can-do' attitude and I am always trying to overcome the issue on my own.

I am able to write responsive pages in React with Typescript in line with the newest standards.

HOW TO REACH ME

Phone: +48 662 623 531

Email: marcin.wrzs@gmail.com

SKILLS

Programming

React, TypeScript, JavaScript, Context API, HTML, CSS (including SASS), bootstrap, webpack, github, SQL

Achievements:

Radio Luz: hosting weekly radio show called Ultradzwięki

Toastmasters: practicing public speaking skills

Aiesec: marketing promotion of the event Dni Kariery

2017

EDUCATION

Reskilled

Programming mentorship - work with senior developers on non commercial project in React + Typescript 2023 to present

Wrocław University of Economics

Master of Finance and Accounting 2017 - 2019

University of Wrocław

Bachelor of National Security 2014 - 2017

PROJECTS

Foodie

View code and demo

Tech Stack: React, cutom Hooks like usePagination, useAxios, useMutation, Typescript, react-router, Context API, ReactSlick.

Foodie is a versatile application that communicate via http with the external Api spoonacular, offering a rich repository of recipes. Seamlessly integrated with a secure backend server for user registration and authentication, Foodie allows users to discover popular recipes and rate them, search by category or name, view detailed recipe information, and build a collection of favorites.

Portfolio

View code

Tech Stack: React, Typescript, Context API, react-router, styled-components, EmailJS.

Introducing a resume application that shows my qualifications and professional achievement. The application is responsible and features both Day and Night modes. In addition, our integrated contact form, powered by EmailJS, allows you to effortlessly connect with me via email.

Blackjack

View code

Tech Stack: HTML, SCSS, Javascript, Webpack.

Project is a copy of a card game called Blackjack, written with Object Oriented Programming principles.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Technical Lead, Broker Accreditation AnalystAxa XL | January 2023 to present

Analyst, Senior Financial Services OperationsFactor Law | October 2020 to December 2022

Security and Pricing Data Management Specialist Credit Suisse | January 2020 to September 2020

Data & Document Specialist
UBS | February 2019 to October 2019

Junior Representative, Reconciliation BNY Mellon | January 2018 to February 2019